CÉSAR GARCÍA CABEZA

Software Engineer graduate

J +34 648035992

Pola de Siero, Spain

themrcesi.github.io

EDUCATION

M.Sc. in Artificial Intelligence

Technical University of Madrid

September 2020 - Present

Madrid, Spain

B.Sc. in Computer Science

Wroclaw University of Science & Technology

2018 - 2019

Wroclaw, Poland

• Erasmus exchange during the academic course 2018/2019.

B.Eng. in Computer Software Engineering

University of Oviedo

2016 - 2020

Oviedo, Spain

- Coursed 204 ECTS in English.
- Average grade: 8.33 (out of 10).

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer Intern

DAIL Software

April 2021 - Present

Research Intern

Biomedical Informatics Group, Technical University of Madrid

September 2020 - September 2020

Undergraduate Research Intern

UNIMODE Research Group, University of Oviedo

September 2019 – October 2019

Oviedo, Spain

The following tasks were performed in collaboration with two professors of the Computation and Artificial Intelligence department:

- Analysis and optimization of algorithms.
- Development of algorithms.

The previous tasks were applied to a specific problem: aggregation of partially ordered sets. This work set a baseline for my Final Degree Project, obtaining later a grade of 10.

LIFE PHILOSOPHY

" Always ready to learn new things. If I have a goal, I don´t stop until I get it."

ABOUT ME

Software engineer graduate with a passion for data, technology & artificial intelligence especially machine and deep learning and its real-life applications such as natural language processing.

I am a passionate lover of sports, having played: football, basketball, volleyball, tennis, panel, fronton, badminton, snowboard... But, without any doubt, Judo is, and will always be, my real passion. Judo has been present in my life since I was 6 years old, and nowadays I have the black belt, 2° DAN. Thanks to this incredible sport I have learnt essential values such as respect, self control, perseverance and overcoming.

STRENGTHS

Motivator & Leader Curious

Hard-working Problem solving

Ability to work in team

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Software Design & Development Pvthon **Computer Vision** Information Retrieval NLP Machine and Deep Learning Web Scrapping Agile Methods Docker Scikit-learn Keras Tensorflow PyTorch Dask Git React Numpy **Pandas**

SCHOLARSHIPS

Erasmus+ Grant

University of Oviedo

September 2018 - June 2019

Oviedo, Spain

Excellent Academic Achievement Scholarship

University of Oviedo

September 2016 - June 2017

Oviedo, Spain

CERTIFICATIONS

Deep Learning Specialization

Coursera

■ January 2021

Skills: Neural Networks, Convolutional Neural Networks, Recurrent Neural Networks, Keras, Tensorflow.

Machine Learning, Data Science and Deep Learning with Python **Udemy**

August 2020

Skills: Python, Numpy, Pandas, Scikit-learn, Machine Learning, Recommender Systems, Neural Networks.

COURSES

First-Aid

Cruz Roja

March 2014 - May 2014

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Volunteer

Erasmus Student Network Oviedo

September 2019 - Present

LANGUAGES

Spanish English French



C1 Advanced

Cambridge Assesment English

= 2017

Delf B1

Alliance Française

= 2015